♪♪～
(土方)あぁ 眠い…｡
Man, I'm sleepy...
うぅ…｡
かれこれ ３日も動きなし｡
Three days without any action.
But he should be making a move soon.
しかし そろそろ
ﾔﾂも動き出すはずだ｡
こちら 土方｡
Hijikata here.
No change here yet.
まだ こっちに変化はねえ｡
そっちは どうなってる？
How's it going over there?
(沖田)ﾗｰｼﾞｬ｡
Roger.
いや ﾗｰｼﾞｬじゃねえよ｡
裏口の状況を聞いてるんだよ｡
No, don't just roger me.
I'm asking how the back door looks.
そっちは どうなってる？
How's it going over there?
I prefer more MSG flavor.
もうちょっと
化学調味料が強いほうが➡
ｵﾚは好きですね｡
[TEL]あっ!?
Huh?
いや こっちの問題です｡
っていうか 味の問題｡
Oh, just an issue on my side.
More like a taste issue.
[Whinery]
[TEL]お前 張り込み中に
なに食ってんだよ！
Why are you eating in the
middle of a stakeout?
[TEL]つか ｽﾞﾙｽﾞﾙうるせえよ！
ちょっと にいちゃん｡
And your slurping's too loud!
Hey, big guy.
You're bothering the other customers.
他のお客に迷惑だからさ
ｹｰﾀｲで話すのは➡
Could you stop talking
on your cell phone?
やめてくんねえかな？
ﾗｰｼﾞｬ｡
Roger.
ﾗｰｼﾞｬじゃねえよ！
さっさと持ち場に…｡
Roger, my ass!
Get back to your post!
(通話の切れる音)
上等だ あの野郎…｡
Bastard...pisses me off.
(銀時)あの～ すみません｡
Uh, excuse me.
どいてもらえます？
ああん!?
Could you move?
Huh? You're...
ｼﾞｬﾏなんすけど｡
ﾃﾒｴは…｡
["Two Is Better Than One. Two
People Are Better Than One."]
あのねぇ あなたね…｡
Look here...
You see?
ここ みんなのｺﾞﾐ捨て場でしょ｡
This is where everybody
throws their trash.
あなた一人が
使ってるわけじゃないでしょ｡
It's not like this place belongs
to you, ya know?
それとも なに？
これ あなたのｺﾞﾐ箱？
Or what?
Is this your trash can?
《寝ぼけてやがる｡
ｵﾚに気づいてねえのか？
He's half asleep.
He hasn't noticed me?
Tch.
ﾁｯ こんなときに
面倒なﾔﾂと出くわしちまった｡
I just had to run into this troublemaker...
相手にしてるﾀｲﾐﾝｸﾞじゃねえ｡
I don't have time to deal with him.
Stuff that belongs to everyone
should be shared by everyone.
みんなのものは みんなのもの｡
あなたのものも
みんなのものだからね｡
Stuff that belongs to you should
be shared by everyone.
Like a reverse Jaian kind of thing.
[Note: Parody of Jaian from Doraemon. His famous
line is "Your stuff is mine, my stuff is mine."]
逆ｼﾞｬｲｱﾝ状態とでもいえばいいの？
公共ﾏﾅｰってのは しっかり
守ってくれないと｡ わかった？
You have to follow the proper
manners for sharing.
Got it?
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
あぁ わかった わかった｡
すまねえな｡
My bad.
なんだ その返事は｡
あ？
What kind of response is that?
You think that's enough to get
you out of any situation?
なんでもかんでも わかったって
言えばいいと思ってるんですか？
結婚３年目の旦那が
倦怠期まっしぐらか!?
Are you like a husband on
his third year of marriage?
Getting weary of the married life?
ったよ！ いいから静かにしてろ！
I get it, so keep it down!
Then look me in the eye!
ったなら
ｵﾚの目見て言え この野郎！
あ…｡
｢あ｣じゃねえよ｡
Ah.
Don't "Ah" me.
It's too early to be dealing
with your blabbing.
朝から うるせえんだよ！
こっちは勤務中だ｡
I'm working here.
So the citizens can pile
up their trash in peace.
市民の皆さんが 安心して
ｺﾞﾐを溜めながら暮らせるようにな｡
しょっぴかれたくなかったら
さっさと ここからうせろ！
So scram if you don't want me
to drag you down to the station!
What are you doing, psycho cop?!
何しやがる この暴力警官！
《心底ﾑｶつく野郎だぜ…》
You're seriously pissing me off!
おいおい ﾏｼﾞかよ｡
Hey, hey, now. You for real?
こんな早朝から 双眼鏡で覗き？
Using binoculars to peep
this early in the morning?
興奮しちゃいましたって
それ あれだよ 性犯罪？
And you're getting all excited?
So you're like a sex offender?
That's not funny.
ｼｬﾚになんないよ それ｡
番組的に ｼｬﾚになんないよ｡
Especially for this show.
誰が覗きだ こら！
うるせえっつってんだろ！
Who are you accusing of peeping?!
I said to stop blabbing!
これ以上 ｼﾞｬﾏすっと
公務執行妨害で➡
If you keep bugging me, I swear I'll arrest
you for obstructing an officer's duties.
ﾏｼﾞ しょっぴくぞ！
やってみろってんだよ！
Go right ahead!
You should take a look
inside your own soul
人の生活覗く前に 自分の心を
ちゃんと覗いてみやがれ｡
before you peep on other people's lives!
Check out one of your embarrassing
childhood memories!
そのまま 少年時代の
恥ずかしい思い出でも➡
覗いてみやがれ！
意外と泣けるぞ！
It might even make you cry!
Huh?
はっ？
公務執行妨害 並びに➡
You're under arrest for interfering
with a police investigation and
insulting a police officer.
警官侮辱罪で 現行犯逮捕｡
That's not funny!
冗談じゃねえよ！
ﾃﾒｴ おとなしく…｡
Behave yourself, damn it!
あっ！
おい 総悟➡
Huh?
Hey, Sogo.
公務執行妨害のﾔﾂを
現行犯逮捕した｡
I arrested someone for interfering
with the investigation.
Take him to the station for me.
ｵﾚの代わりに 署まで連行しろ｡
ﾗｰｼﾞｬ｡
おやっさん 替え玉 ﾊﾞﾘｶﾀで｡
Roger.
Pops, give me some more
noodles, extra firm.
ﾗｰｼﾞｬ！
(土方)ﾗｰｼﾞｬじゃねえよ！
Roger!
Roger, my ass!
なに替え玉してんだよ！
すぐ来い！ すぐ！
Why are you ordering more noodles?!
Get your ass over here now!
You're late.
おせえよ！
旦那… 何してんですかい？
Master, whatcha doing?
何もやってねえよ｡
不当逮捕だよ こんなの｡
Nothing at all.
This is an unlawful arrest.
ｵﾚは やってないよ これ｡
I didn't do anything.
Sogo, you aren't doing your job anyway,
総悟 お前どうせ
仕事してねえんだから➡
so take him down to the
station and lock him up.
ｺｲﾂを 署まで連行して
ﾌﾞﾁ込んどけ｡
I can't do that.
そうはいきやせんねぇ｡
ｵﾚには 命よりも
任務のほうが 大事ですから｡
My duty comes before my life.
さっきまで ﾗｰﾒﾝ食ってたの
誰だよ！
Who was the one eating
ramen a moment ago?!
あれ… あれ？ 鍵がねえな｡
Huh?
Er, the key's gone.
What?
なに!?
おい 総悟➡
Hey, Sogo.
Use your key to unlock us.
お前の鍵で 外してくれ｡
Yeah, get these off.
おう 外せ 外せ｡
ちょっと なにこれ!? 沖田君!?
ｵﾚにつけて どうすんだよ！
Hey. What is this, Okita-kun?
Why are you cuffing me?!
じゃ ｵﾚ 持ち場に戻るんで｡
I'm going back to my post now.
(２人)え～っ!?
沖田君!?
っつか 外せこれ！
Okita-kun!
Get these off us! What are you thinking?!
何考えてんだ ﾃﾒｴ！
Well, don't you think...
だって そっちのほうが…➡
it's a lot more fun this way?
なんか おもしろそうじゃ
ないすか｡
Then I'll be going.
じゃ ｵﾚ行くんで｡
Hey, hold up!
Damn it, Sogo!
ちょっと ｷﾐ！
おいｺﾗ！ 総悟 待てﾃﾒｴ…｡
Fine!
わかった 鍵よこせ！
鍵だけよこせ！
Give me the key!
Just give me the key!
I told you to give me the
''key''! Not mayonnaise!
鍵よこせっつったんだよ！
つか なんでﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞ!?
What are you talking about?
なに言ってんですかい｡
Aren't you always keen
about mayonnaise?
ﾏﾖは いつでも
ｱﾝﾀのｷｰﾎﾟｲﾝﾄじゃねぇですかい｡
うまい！ うまいけど
いらないよ➡
Clever!
Very clever, but we don't
need any puns right now!
そんな 小じゃれたｾﾘﾌ！
Take care of yourselves then.
じゃあ お二人とも
養生してくだせえ｡
Hey! Okita-kun!
うぉ～い 沖田君！
早まっちゃいかん！
Don't be so hasty!
人生もっと
ﾎﾟｼﾞﾃｨﾌﾞに考えていこう！
You should have a more
positive outlook on life!
総悟 総悟 ﾃﾒｴ聞けよ➡
Sogo!
Sogo, listen up, damn it!
あとで ぶっ殺すぞ ﾃﾒｴ 総悟！
I'm gonna kill you later, Sogo!
お～い 沖田君！
戻ってくるんだよね!?
Hey, Okita-kun!
You're coming back, right?!
上司の言うこと聞かなきゃね！
総悟 ｺﾗ～！
You're going to listen to
your superior, right?!
Damn it, Sogo!
Don't look at me.
(２人)こっち見んな｡
Hey, hey, hey... Give me a break.
《おいおいおい
勘弁してくれよ これ｡
なんで こんな 歩く電撃ｲﾗｲﾗ棒
みたいなﾔﾂと➡
Why do I have to be stuck with
Mr. Master-of-pissing-me-off?
こんな状態に
なんなきゃいけねえんだ!?》
Hold on a sec.
《ちょっと待ってくれよ これ｡
まだ 今朝の占い 見てねえよ｡
I didn't check my horoscope today.
How does taking out the trash lead to
being paired with throbby-vein-boy?
なんで ｺﾞﾐ捨てに来ただけで
こんな青筋野郎と➡
ﾍﾟｱにされてんの!? これ》
At this rate, all of my investigating
will have been for nothing.
《このままじゃ 今までの捜査が
台なしになっちまう！》
In any case, I need to get
out of this situation pronto!
《とにかく ここは 一刻も早く➡
この状況から
脱出するしかねえ！》
Ack!
うぉっ！ ﾎｼが動いた！
Target's on the move!
っつか ﾃﾒｴ なんで
そっち行ってんだ ｺﾗ！
Hey! Why are you going that way?!
I'm headed for the station.
ｱﾝﾀらの屯所に行くんだよ｡
They've got a spare key
for the handcuffs, right?
手錠の合鍵くらい あるだろ？
What are you babbling about?!
なに こんなときに
ふざけてんだよ！
We've been chasing this radical Anti-Foreigner
Faction member for over a month!
ｱｲﾂは ｵﾚたちが
１か月以上もかけて追ってた➡
過激派攘夷浪士の一人
指名手配中の野郎だって！
He's on the wanted list...
はいはい もう それはいいから➡
Yeah, yeah. Whatever.
屯所行って さっさとこれ
外そうぜ｡
Let's go to the station and get these off.
この機を逃すと １か月の苦労が
水の泡になっちまうってのが➡
A month of work will go down
the drain if I miss this chance!
わかんねえのか！
Can't you understand?!
Drain schmain. You can play
cops and robbers later.
水の泡でも 泡姫でもいいよ｡
さっさと ﾌﾘｰﾀﾞﾑ＆ｼﾞｬｽﾃｨｽ
よこせよ！
Give me my freedom and justice already!
最悪のﾀｲﾐﾝｸﾞだ｡
The worst possible timing...
Hey, Sogo!
おい 総悟 ﾎｼが動いた｡
追え｡ おい 総悟！
Target's on the move!
Follow him!
Hey, Sogo!
Bah! After him!
ﾁｯ 追うぞ｡
ｱﾀﾀｯ｡ ﾃﾒｴ｡
Hey!
The girl you like will run away
if you're always on the chase!
追いかけてばかりじゃ 好きな
あの子は逃げるだけなんだよ｡
ここでﾔﾂを
逃がすわけにはいかねえんだよ｡
I can't let him get away now!
関係ねえな｡
ﾃﾒｴ 公務執行妨害で逮捕する｡
It's got nothing to do with me!
I'm going to arrest you
for obstructing justice.
もう逮捕されてるよ｡
I've already been arrested!
Cut it out already!
(２人)いい加減にしろ ﾃﾒｴ！
Justice!
ｼﾞｬｽﾃｨｽ！
それが 人にものを頼む態度か
この野郎！
Is this how you ask someone
for a favor, bastard?!
《そうだ｡ 今はｺｲﾂを説得しねえ
ことには なにも始まらねえんだ｡
He's right...
I have to convince him to help
or else nothing will get done.
ｺｲﾂに頼んで…》
I'll have to ask him...
なにしてんだ？
決心してんだよ｡
What are you doing?
None of your business!
あぁ その… 攘夷浪士を
一緒に追ってほしいっつ～か➡
Uh, well...
Could you help me chase down an
Anti-Foreigner Faction fugitive?
Or yeah, something...like that...
まあ そんな感じ… みたいな｡
あぁ～ん？
Well?
Huh?
That's not good enough, Hijikata.
[無線](沖田)そんなんじゃ
足んねえんだよ 土方｡
[無線]ちゃんと地面に手ついて
土下座しろ｡
You need to get down on
your knees and beg.
うるせえっつ～か お前
犯人追えよ！
Shove it!
And chase the fugitive, damn it!
そうだよ 土下座だよ｡
That's right. On your knees.
That's the standard procedure for
asking a favor, Hijikata-kun.
人にものを頼むときは
それが基本だよね 土方君｡
Fine.
わかったよ｡ はい 土下座！
Okay! I'm down on my knees!
うおっ｡
はい 土下座｡
Please help me chase the fugitive!
ｵﾚと一緒に犯人を追ってください｡
Okay! I'm down on my knees!
はい 土下座！
痛っ 痛いって｡
Ow! That hurts!
Okay! I'm down on my knees!
はい 土下座｡
やめろ｡
なんでだよ？
Cut it out!
Why?!
ｵﾒｴが来ないかぎり
手錠が外れないのはわかった｡
Well I won't get these handcuffs
off until you agree to come.
とりあえず 言うとおりに
してやるから ﾊﾟﾌｪおごれ｡
I'll do as you say for now,
so buy me a parfait.
Later.
あとでな｡ 今はﾔﾂから
目を離すわけにはいかねえんだよ｡
I can't take my eyes off him right now.
Just capture him already.
さっさと捕まえちまえよ
あんなの｡
It can't be that hard.
難しいことじゃねえだろ｡
Our goal isn't to catch him.
ｱｲﾂ一人を捕まえるのが
目的じゃねえ｡
Our ultimate goal is to follow him to their
base and round up the whole lot.
ﾔﾂらのｱｼﾞﾄを突き止め
一網打尽にするのが最大の目的よ｡
一網打尽だが
大魔人だか知らねえが➡
Lot schmot.
Forget the tedious stuff
and get this over with.
めんどくせえことやらずに
さっさと終わらせろや｡
うるせえ｡ 素人は黙ってろ！
Shut up!
Amateurs should keep their mouths shut!
[無線](沖田)土方 ﾃﾒｴ
手伝ってもらってる分際で➡
Hijikata, you're acting way too arrogant towards
someone who's helping you out.
偉そうなんだよ｡
さんづけで呼べよ こら｡
Be more polite.
I don't wanna hear another
word outta you!
ｵﾒｴは もっと黙ってろ！
And stop staring at us!
つか 見てんじゃねえ！
We're following him in.
ｵﾚたちも入るぞ｡ 自然にしてろよ｡
Act natural.
って どこが自然？
How is this natural?!
Well, you know?
いや あれだよ｡
親がﾀﾞﾝｻｰだったから➡
We're going with the story that
our parents were dancers
自然と
ﾀﾞﾝｽが身についたって設定で｡
so we have a natural tendency to dance.
自然のﾎﾟｲﾝﾄがちげえよ｡
That's not what I meant by natural.
[無線](沖田)いや まず
ﾊﾞﾗくわえてるとこ突っ込めよ｡
Uh, you should say something
about the rose first.
Where the hell are you
watching us from?!
ｵﾒｴはさっきからどこで見てんだ？
Sorry to keep you waiting.
お待たせしました｡
ﾃﾒｴ どういうつもりだ？
What do you think you're doing?
え？ ふつうに
ﾊﾟﾌｪ食ってるだけだけど｡
I'm just eating this parfait.
You screwed up my aim with the mayonnaise
when you moved your arm.
ｵﾒｴが腕動かすと
ｵﾚのﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞの照準が狂うんだよ｡
なんだよ ﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞの照準って？
What do you need mayonnaise for?
Why are you adding mayonnaise
to coffee?
つか なんで ｺｰﾋｰにﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞ？
Mayonnaise is an all-mighty
universal condiment
ﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞは
万物森羅万象に対応できる➡
that works on everything and anything.
ｵｰﾙﾏｲﾃｨｰｱｲﾃﾑなんだよ｡
Are you an idiot?
ﾊﾞｯｶじゃねえの｡
あぁ～！
Damn it! Don't ruin my parfait!
ﾃﾒｴ ｵﾚのﾊﾟﾌｪ
汚すんじゃねえよ ｺﾗ！
汚してねえ!!
ぐわぁ～！
I didn't ruin it!
ﾌﾝ… 素人が…｡
Damn amateur...
Hijikata-san. Hijikata-san.
[無線](沖田)土方さん 土方さん｡
ん？ 何だ？
[無線](沖田)そういや…➡
What is it?
I just remembered that I forgot
to tell you something.
さっき 言ってなかったことが
あるんでさぁ…｡
(土方)うん？
[無線](沖田)
さっきの ﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞですがね…｡
That mayonnaise I gave you...
土方君…｡
Hi-ji-ka-ta-kun...
[無線](沖田)中に
下剤を入れちまったんでさぁ…｡
Had laxative in it.
ｳﾝｺ… したくなっちゃった｡
I need to take a shit.
ｳｿ…｡
No way.
♪♪～
(２人)ぐぉ～っ!!
ちょちょ… ちょっと待て！
H-H-H-Hold it right there!
んだ ｺﾗ！ この状況で待てるか！
What is it?
I can't wait any longer!
考えてみろ｡
同じ個室に２人でﾄｲﾚ｡
Think for a second.
Can both of us take a
crap in the same stall?
そんなこと できるのお前！
できね～っ！
We can't!
お前 それこそ ﾄｲﾚでﾗﾝﾃﾞﾌﾞｰだよ｡
That'd be like a rendezvous
in the restroom.
お腹が乱れて 乱でﾌﾞｰだよ ｺﾚ！
A rendezvous with our bowels in agony!
(土方)確かに…
考えただけで恐ろしいが…｡
You're right...
That thought is scary enough.
What do we do then?!
じゃあ どうするってんだ～!!
力入れるな～！
Don't get too worked up.
ｵ… ｵﾚたちには 知恵も紙もある｡
We have knowledge and
paper on our side!
何とか最善策を考えるんだ…｡
We can come up with the
best possible plan...
まず ﾌﾟﾗﾝＡ｡
Let's start with plan A.
１人は用を足し
１人は扉の上の外で待機…｡
One of us conducts his business while
the other waits on top of the door.
ただし
これは待機している人間が➡
But there's the risk that the person
waiting will have to watch the act.
現場を目撃しなければならない
というﾘｽｸが伴う…｡
ﾌﾟﾗﾝＢは…｡
What's plan B?
B...
Ｂ… 外で待機している人間が
扉から手を突っ込む…｡
The person waiting outside sticks
his hand through the door.
しかし これは
扉に鍵をかけられない…➡
But then the door can't be
completely shut or locked.
というﾃﾞﾒﾘｯﾄが生じる…｡
Plan C...
ﾌﾟﾗﾝＣ…｡
ﾌﾟﾗﾝＣ！
Plan C...
鍵も閉めて現場の目撃も
回避できるかわりに➡
While allowing the door to be locked and
avoiding having to witness the act,
用を足す者は
低姿勢を保ち続ける必要があり➡
the person conducting his business
must bend down,
待機している者は
床との接地面が広い➡
while the person waiting risks having
to lay down on the floor.
…というﾘｽｸを
負わなければならない！
さぁ どうする…｡
Now which one do you want?
The unlocked door is a problem,
but I'll go with plan B.
鍵を閉められねえ
という欠点はあるが➡
ｵﾚは ﾌﾟﾗﾝＢでいく！
Same here.
ｵﾚもだ！ あとは 順番だけだ！
All that's left is to decide the order.
First comes rock.
(２人)最初はｸﾞｰ！ ｼﾞｬﾝｹﾝ ﾎﾟﾝ！
Rock, paper, scissors!
Alright!
おっしゃ～！
いや 待て｡ あと出しだろ 今｡
No, wait.
You went after I did.
この非常時に
言いがかりつけてんじゃねえ！
There's no time for false accusations
in this emergency!
いや 非常時だからこそ！
No! An emergency is
exactly the time for it!
(２人)譲れねえ～!!
I won't let you go!
We're screwed!
[Plan A, Plan B, Plan C]
ｼﾞｬﾊﾟﾆｰｽﾞｽﾀｲﾙ…｡ ｼﾞｬﾊﾟﾆｰｽﾞｽﾀｲﾙ｡
Japanese-style...!
Japanese-style...
体の向きを前後逆にすれば
何とかなるが➡
It'll work if we face each other,
屈む姿勢が
絶対の このｽﾀｲﾙでは➡
but the lack of height means that
plan A will no longer work!
高さを必要とする
Ａﾌﾟﾗﾝは成り立たない…｡
しかも このﾄｲﾚは
扉から便器までの距離が➡
And there's too much distance between the
toilet and the door so plan B's also out...
ﾑﾀﾞにありやがる｡ ﾌﾟﾗﾝＢも…｡
Ｃも厳しいぞ ｺｲﾂは…｡
C will be tough, too...
つ… つまり…｡
Which means...
もう 限界だ…｡
I can't take anymore...
もう… ﾀﾞﾒ…｡
No more...
ｵﾚたちに…｡
Has God...
(土方)救いの神はいないのか…｡
...forsaken us?
いや待て… まだﾌﾟﾗﾝＤがある｡
No, wait...
There's still plan D.
ﾌﾟﾗﾝＤ… だと？
Plan D, you say...?
ﾌﾟﾗﾝＤ…｡
Plan D...
The other person does a handstand above
the person conducting his business.
用を足す者の頭上で
逆立ちをするという離れ業｡
鍵も閉めて 他者からの目撃を
回避できる代わりに➡
The door's locked,
and the person above won't
have to witness the act,
上に下に
体力を使わなければならない➡
but both people must be strong enough
for this prohibited and risky maneuver.
禁断にして命懸けの戦法だ｡
んなことが できるのか？ 本当に｡
やるしかねえ！
Is that even possible?!
We have no choice!
(２人)ん～！
Hijikata-san. Odd Jobs Master.
[無線](沖田)土方さん 万事屋の旦那
大丈夫ですか～い？
You okay in there?
(２人)うるせえ！
Shut up!
(ﾄｲﾚの水を流す音)
ﾃﾒｴ 長すぎなんだよ｡
腕がしびれたじゃねえか｡
You took way too long.
My arms are all numb.
ｵﾒｴは 紙 使いすぎなんだよ｡
You used too much paper.
I only had 10 cm to use.
ｵﾚの分 10ｾﾝﾁしか
残ってなかったろうが｡
ん？
ﾁｯ！ 逃がしてたまるか！
I won't let him get away!
停まれ 警察だ！
Stop! This is the police!
うわぁ！
うわぁ～っ！
ﾃﾒｴ どけ！ 見えねえ！
Move, damn it! I can't see!
There's a truck! A truck!
ﾄﾗｯｸ来る ﾄﾗｯｸ！ 右 右！
Right! Right!
ﾊﾞｶか そっちじゃねえ！
Stupid! Not that way!
右っつったろ！
お箸を持つほうだよ ﾊﾞｶ！
You told me to go right!
The side you hold your
chopsticks with, idiot!
ﾊﾞｶとは何だ ﾊﾞｶ！ うわ～！
Who are you calling an idiot, idiot?!
I'll kill you!
ﾃﾒｴ 殺す！ 右だっつ～の ﾊﾞｶ！
I said to go right, idiot!
黙りやがれ！
うわぁ！
Shut the hell up!
何しやがる！
右に行っただろうが このﾀｺ！
What are you doing?!
I went right, dumbass!
ｵﾚから見て右だろ 普通！
I meant my right, obviously!
大人は 人の目線に立って
物事を考えろ！
Adults are supposed to be smart enough
to see from another person's perspective!
うるせえ！
Shut up!
Besides, you should have realized
that the second time around!
だいたい二度目くらいは
気づいてもいいだろうが！
As if I'm going to follow your orders!
誰が お前の指図に従うか！
もう わかんねえよ すでに！
I can't even tell anymore!
That's what I should be saying!
こっちのｾﾘﾌだ ﾊﾞｶ野郎！
Okay...
よし なんとか突き止めたぜ｡
We somehow managed
to track him down.
Hold on...
待ってやがれ｡
まだ やんのかよ…｡
You're not done yet?
おい総悟 応援 頼む｡ おい総悟！
Hey, Sogo.
Send reinforcements.
まだ ﾑﾀﾞだってのが
わからねえのか？
Haven't you realized that's
a waste of time?
Tch.
ﾁｯ… しようがねえな｡
Guess I have no choice.
おいおい土方君 何考えてんの？
Hey, now. Hijikata-kun.
What do you have in mind?
ひょっとして
このまま乗り込もうとか➡
Don't tell me you're going to barge in.
考えちゃったりしてるわけ？
当たりめえだろ｡
Of course I am.
ここまで来といて
ﾁｬﾝｽを潰すわけにはいかねえ｡
I can't let this chance slip
away after coming so far.
ｵﾚ 疲れてきちゃったんだけど｡
I'm pretty tired...
土下座すっぞ こら！
Want me to get down
on my knees again?
うむ ご苦労｡
Good work.
Nobody noticed you, right?
誰にも気づかれて
いないだろうな？
Of course not!
もちろんでさ｡
よし 港に船が着いてる｡
Good...
There's a boat in the harbor.
ﾌﾞﾂを運んで さっさとｽﾞﾗかるぞ｡
(みんな)へい！
Move the stuff and escape.
Yes!
ｸｿｯ！ そうは…｡
Damn it. I won't let...
[無線](沖田)土方さん
呼びましたか～い？
Hijikata-san, you rang?
Idiot!
ﾊﾞｶ… あっ！
[無線]土方さん
ﾎｼの野郎は どうしましたい？
Hijikata-san.
What happened to the target?
Hijikata-san?
[無線]土方さ～ん？
誰かいるぞ！
Somebody's here!
やべっ！
ｵﾒｴが通信機落とすから！
Crap!
You just had to drop your radio!
うるせえ！
Shut up!
うわっ！ ６を返して９にする｡
Flip over so I can land on you!
なんだ ﾈｽﾞﾐ２匹か｡
Oh, we've got two rats here.
たった２人で いい度胸だな｡
You two have guts to sneak
in by yourselves.
しかも手錠してやがるぜ｡
And they're handcuffed.
仲のいいこった！
Friendly guys, huh?
仲が…｡
Friendly...
いいだと…｡
Guys, you say...?
仲よく あの世へ行けや～！
You can go to the next world together!
誰が仲がいいんだ？
こんなﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞ依存症と！
Who did you just accuse of being friendly
with this mayonnaise addict?!
ﾏﾖﾈｰｽﾞに謝れ この糖分ﾌｪﾁが！
Apologize to mayonnaise,
you sugar freak!
がぁ～っ！
真撰組副長
土方十四郎だ この野郎！
I'm the Shinsengumi Vice-Chief,
Toshiro Hijikata, damn it!
ｵﾒｴら！ 公務執行妨害ならびに
警官侮辱罪の逮捕者だ ﾊﾞｶ野郎!!
You're all under arrest for interfering
with a police investigation and
insulting a police officer, dumbasses!
笑わせやがる｡ やっちまえ！
What a laugh.
Kill them!
♪♪～
どぁ～！
なんだｺｲﾂら！ 化け物か!?
Wh-Who are these guys?
Are they monsters?
♪♪～
何やってんだ！ 一気にかかれ～!!
What are you doing?!
Attack all at once!
(土方)うぉ～！
どりゃ～!!
うぉ～！
うわ～！
わぁ～！
ｸｯｿｰ！ なんてｺﾝﾋﾞﾈｰｼｮﾝだ！
Damn it!
What a crazy combo!
ﾃﾒｴら！
なんだかんだ仲いいじゃねえか!!
For all your talk, you guys
sure are getting along fine!
(２人)よくねえよ！
Hell no!
Die together!
一緒に死ねや～！
I said...
(２人)よくねえって…
言ってんだろうが!!
...we're not together!
どぁ～！
おやまぁ…｡
Well, well...
おっせえよ｡
始末書だぞ ﾃﾒｴ｡
You're late.
You get to clean this mess up.
ﾁｸｼｮｳ！
覚えてやがれ！
Damn it...
We won't forget this!
(２人)ﾌｩｰ｡
いや～ やっぱり
始末書じゃすまねえな これは｡
Pretty sure this will take more
than a simple clean-up.
Now, now.
まぁまぁ 終わりよければ
すべてよしでしょう｡
All's well that end's well.
結果ｵｰﾗｲってことで｡
で どうします？
Everything worked out in the end.
So what do we do?
Do I take Master down to the station?
旦那 しょっぴきましょうかい？
たしか 公務執行妨害と➡
Interfering with a police investigation
and insulting a police officer, was it?
警官侮辱罪
じゃなかったでしたっけ？
Hey, now.
おいおい 冗談じゃねえよ！
That's not funny!
You're still going to drag
me down there?!
このうえに
まだ しょっぴかれんのか？
やめとけ 総悟｡
ん？
Forget it, Sogo.
当分 ｿｲﾂの顔は見たくねえよ｡
I don't want to see his face for a while.
ﾊﾞｶ野郎！ それは こっちのｾﾘﾌだ!!
Moron!
That's what I should be saying.
ﾌｯ！
やっぱり仲がいいですねぇ
お二人とも｡
The two of them really do get along.
ﾁｯ｡
ｹｯ｡
(銀時/土方)仲よくねえって｡
We don't get along.
[Preview]
Almost a week has passed since
Dragon Quest IX came out.
[Note: Dragon Quest IX came
out on July 11th in Japan.]
Did everyone beat it already?
I haven't yet.
That's bad.
I'll miss out on all the chatter.
Don't spoil the name of
the last boss for me!
Okay, then next week's GinTama
won't be aired until I beat it.
["Smooth Polygons Smooth Man's Hearts Too"]
Hell no!
[An accident occurs in Tama's body.
It's caused by a computer virus.]
[Next time: Tama Quest... Game start!]
[See you next time]